

# Ali Çınaroğlu

# FRONT-END DEVEOPLER & WORDPRESS EXPERT

+90 (505) 2848980 https://www.alicinaroglu.com

### **Summary**

Professional front end web developer / web application developer with about 10 years of experience. I have had the opportunity to work with very small local companies to start ups to very large international companies.

I have continually worked on multiple projects with varying timelines and objectives concurrently. While maintaining communication as well as meeting deadlines.

I am highly driven and forever curious developer, constantly pursuing information related to our field to continue to push the boundaries and breathe life into projects.

I am a stickler for details and write 100% valid markup. I do not simply use Javascript, jQuery, PHP I actually author my own classes, function and libraries when needed.

I have located to Ankara Turkey and am seeking an energetic, positive position with a local advertising agency or development firm in Germany.

#### **Skills**

- HTML
- HTML5
- CSS
- CSS3
- jQuery
- jQuery UI
- AJAX
- JSON
- JSONP
- JavaScript
- PHP
- Wordpress
- Joomla

- Twitter Bootstrap
- MySQL
- .htaccess
- Adobe Creative Suite
- Mac OS
- Microsoft Office
- Cross-browser
- Compatibility
- SEC
- Web Applications
- User Experience
- Social Media Google
- Analytics

# **Experience**

# Mega Hafıza **Web Developer**

04 / 2014 - 07 / 2015

My day to day activities include developing websites, landing pages and internal applications using technology like HTML5, CSS3, JS, AJAX, SASS and GitHub as well as maintaining existing client websites. This include writing custom modules & bug fixes for numerous CMS systems including Joomla, Word Press and more. I also work with our strategists on various technologies and implementation strategies for our varying projects to help ensure a successful launch.

	Be7 Proje <b>Team Leader</b>	04 / 2013 - 11 / 2013
	Cook - Sedat Tahir Graphic Designer	04 / 2010 - 01 / 2012
	Birnumaram E-Commerce Front End Developer	08 / 2008 - 03 / 2010
	Karya International  Graphic Designer	12 / 2007 - 08 / 2008
	Akanus Bilisim <b>Web Developer</b>	03 / 2007 - 12 / 2007
Interests	Football, History, Pc and Console games, Collector vinyls and retro products.	
Personal	Product of 1984 :) Sporter and Non smoker, and ability to drive cars with B Class License	
Education	Bilkent University - Ankara Turkey	2005